Before we set up the development environment, I just wanted to talk about the dev kits available from
impressive.
And also mentioned the deep kits that I've used while creating this course that you open the link in
the resources available for this video called Development Board Overviews.
You'll find a list of available test kits from impressive any USP.
Thirty two should work fine.
However, just till you're fully aware I've created this course using the first three in the list.
The debt could see the rover kit, as well as the Peko kit, so be sure to look into the Getting Started
guide for yours and browse of the information provided here.
You'll find just about everything that you need to know about your hardware, including the functional
description.
And tell us about your board.
The head of bloc, which includes the name and function of the ILO hairpins, as well as the pin layout.
This is a good way to get familiar with your hard work.
Also, you can find the schematics and the data sheet at the bottom of the page.
And if you happen to use the rover kit, there's additional points of interest to take note of.
The functional description provides you with labels for each component, which is nice.
But what's really worth noting are the setup options shown here.
Be sure to include jumpers where necessary as shown, as well as the jumper shown further down under
the initial setup for enabling USB and are.
Further to the death kit, if you open the second link in the resources, you may need to install and
configure USB drivers so that the ESP 32 is recognized by your machine.
You can follow instructions specific to you operating system shown here.
However, this should be taken care of by the eclipse installation that will do in the following lessons,
but just know that you can come back here if the development kit isn't recognized by your computer.
Just follow the instructions step by step, and you should be good to go.